<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vavada</string>
    <string name="file_chooser_title" translatable="false">choose file</string>
    <string name="cannot_open_file_chooser_txt" translatable="false">Open file</string>
    <string name="please_acce">\nPLEASE ACCEPT OUR \\ TO USE AN APP</string>
    <string name="please_acce_police" underline="true">PRIVACY POLICY</string>

    <string name="Slot_Machines">A slot machine is a gambling game with spinning reels. Those reels 
have symbols on them, which land randomly after you place a bet and spin the reels. 
If these symbols line up, you win prizes based on which symbols fall on that 
“payline”.</string>
    <string name="Roullette">Roulette is a game of chance. It uses a spinning wheel with either 37 or 
38 numbered pockets. The roulette wheel is spun one way and a ball is sent round 
the other way.</string>
    <string name="Poker">Poker is a card game that involves betting with chips and keeping a straight 
face. You can also play poker online and make any kind of face you want.</string>
    <string name="BlackJack">Is a a gambling game using cards; the object is to hold cards having a 
higher count than those dealt to the banker up to but not exceeding 2</string>
    <string name="Baccarat"> A baccarat game is a classic Bond-movie setting, which perhaps makes 
the game seem more intimidating than it should. Baccarat is actually a simple game 
to play. And in terms of betting, the baccarat strategy has much in common with coin 
flips. </string>
    <string name="Lotteries"> A lottery is a form of gambling that involves the drawing of numbers at
random for a prize. Some governments outlaw lotteries, while others endorse it to
the extent of organizing a national or state lottery. It is common to find some degree
of regulation of lottery by governments.</string>
    
    <string name="Randomness_in_slots">This is by far the most important tip you need to know when
playing slots. The machines are completely random and no previous events have
any impact on what will happen next.\n\nThey’re just designed this way. So if you get advice from someone that you should 
take a seat at a certain machine that hasn’t paid out in a while because it’s due to 
pay out, then just ignore it. You should always play on the machines that provide you 
with the most enjoyment and are within your bankroll to play.</string>
    <string name="Progressive_jackpots">This is usually the case when the jackpot has 
been recently won and therefore it’s back to being quite low. What 
you also need to be aware of is that on these slots a small amount 
from what you bet on a spin is automatically taken and added to the 
jackpot.</string>
    <string name="Reviewing_the_playtable">Each machine has an associated pay table 
that will outline to you what it takes to win. The table will show each 
of the machines symbols and provide advice on how many of these 
you need in a line to achieve a win.
Symbols have different values, from the most common ones to the 
rare ones, and then the more symbols you get on a pay line the 
more you win.</string>
    <string name="Playing_slowly">Slots are designed to be played very quickly as this 
will result in the biggest possible intake for the casino that houses it.
Because of this you should take your time in playing slots and don’t 
continuously spin immediately after the preceding spin finishes. 
Take some time and analyze the slot face and see how you won, or 
how you missed out on this occasion.</string>
    <string name="Studying_the_bonus_rounds">On video slots, the most entertaining part 
of playing is when you hit a bonus feature. These will give you the 
opportunity to win big, although sometimes you won’t win much at 
all.\n
Bonus features usually result in free spins or offer bonus cash 
prizes. Each machine is different when it comes to hitting the bonus 
so make sure you check out the pay table to see what’s required to 
get into the round.</string>
    <string name="Make_sure_you_have_fun">Although I’ve provided you with some great
tips here on how to increase your chances of winning and how to
play slots in the best possible way, the most important thing is that
you’re having fun while you play.
I always play slots for fun, whether it’s to have a few free drinks
while I play Wheel of Fortune slots in Vegas with my friends, or just
to pass 30 minutes while I’m waiting for my poker tournament to
start, it’s always about fun.</string>
</resources>